Christofer Saputra

Web Developer | HR Graduate

HR Management graduate and a self-taught developer since 2019. I am passionate in technologies and love to take on challenges and learn new knowledge. I specializes in Django for the backend and React.js for the frontend. Looking for a position in either *Junior Backend* or *Frontend Engineer*.

christ290500@gmail.com

Malang, East Java, Indonesia

in linkedin.com/in/christofer-saputra-722b1b186

+62 85692252480

chromium7.github.io/chromium7/

github.com/chromium7

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Human Resource Management and Management

Curtin University of Technology

11/2017 - 11/2019

Courses

 Distinction in International HRM, Performance and Conflict Management, Strategic Rewards Management, Selecting and Promoting Staffs.

 Course Weighted Average of 72.54/100. Singapore

 High Distinction in Business Ethics, Intro to Accounting, Economics and Marketing.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

E-commerce Web App (11/2020 - 12/2020)

- https://github.com/chromium7/mangovodo
- A responsive designed dynamic website, built ready for production using Django, Docker, Postgres, Gunicorn, Nginx, Redis and Celery

Algorithms Visualizer (12/2020 - Present)

- https://github.com/chromium7/algorithm-visualizer
- Visualize and explains how algorithms work behind the scene
- Algorithms include: Karatsuba, Sorting, Shortest Path and more

Online Chat Web App (01/2021 - 02/2021)

- https://github.com/chromium7/django-chat-room
- Real-time users interactive chat room built with Django, JavaScript and WebSockets
- Deployed to Heroku

WORK EXPERIENCE

Shop Manager

Mebel Lancar Jaya Malang

11/2019 - Present Malang

Tasks

- Manages daily operations: selling, assembling and delivering products.
- Keeps track and handles the shop's inventory.
- Maintains good relationship with suppliers and customers.

Python Tutor Self-managed

08/2020 - Present

Online

Tasks

- Teaches basic Python to friends who want to start programming / data science.
- Prepare practice questions and review codes.
- Helped a computer science student achieve an A+ in a Python course.

SKILLS



ACHIEVEMENTS

8th place Indonesian Young Coders League 2021 (04/2021)

IYCL is a coding competition held by Mekari and Money Forward in Indonesia which was participated by almost 1000 participants.

CERTIFICATES

CS50W Web Programming with Python and JavaScript at Harvard EdX (07/2020 - 12/2020)

 $\label{lem:https://certificates.cs50.io/a1f90e84-86c3-453a-bafe-f31486f4d750.pdf2 size=letter$

CS50X Introduction to Computer Science at Harvard Edx (01/2021 - 01/2021)

 $\label{lem:https://certificates.cs50.io/473179e3-d2d0-4c23-84fb-5c22ef703644.pdf? \\ \underline{size=letter}$

CS50 Introduction to Artificial Intelligence at Harvard Edx (01/2021 - 02/2021)

 $\frac{https://certificates.cs50.io/bb984414-9aaf-4d7a-a545-b391cf10e44b.pdf?}{size=letter}$

LANGUAGES

English

Indonesian

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Chinese

Limited Working Proficiency

INTERESTS

